<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="dialog_title_onboarding">Welcome to Dutch Blitz Scorer!</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_onboarding">Please note that you must own the physical Dutch Blitz card game for this app to be useful.
        \n\nThis app is designed to make scoring for Dutch Blitz simpler.
        \n\nThere are more instructions on the <b>Info</b> tab, but here are some quick tips:
        \n<b>1.</b> To start a new game, press <b>New Game</b>
        \n<b>2.</b> Configure your game settings and press <b>Start Game</b> to begin
        \n<b>3.</b> After each round of Dutch Blitz, press <b>Record new round</b> to record the scores
        \n\nIf you need additional help along the way, tap the <b>Help</b> icon in the top right corner of the screen. It will provide specific help based on the screen you are on.
        \n\nThe home page serves as a history for all games, where you can resume or review games.
        \n\nEnjoy!
    </string>

    <string name="dialog_title_delete_selected_games">Delete selected games</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_delete_selected_games">Are you sure you want to delete the selected games?</string>

    <string name="dialog_title_restart_required">App restart required for dynamic color changes</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_restart_required">The app won\'t be automatically relaunched. The next time you relaunch it, the dynamic color setting will be applied.</string>

    <string name="dialog_title_edit_delete_tip">Edit or delete a round</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_edit_delete_tip">Long press on the round number to edit or delete that round.</string>

    <string name="dialog_title_zero_scores">All zero scores</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_zero_scores">It seems like all the scores are zero 😮.
        \n\nAre you sure you want to continue with saving?</string>

    <string name="dialog_title_quit_create">Quit Creating New Game</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_quit_create">Are you sure you want to go back?
        \n\nGame settings will not be saved as the game was not started.</string>

    <!-- Help dialogs -->
    <string name="dialog_title_help_create_game">Setup New Game Help</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_help_create_game">This screen is for setting up a new game.
        \n\nGive the game a name or leave it as the default.
        \n\nChoose the number of players.
        \nNote: Dutch Blitz normally only supports 4 players unless you own the expansion pack!
        \n\nGive each player a unique name.
        \n\nThen press <b>Start Game</b> to begin!
    </string>

    <string name="dialog_title_help_game_scoring">Game Scoring Help</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_help_game_scoring">This screen shows an overview of each round and each player\'s total score.
        \n\nTo record a new round, use the <b>Record new round</b> button!
        \n\nTo edit or delete a round, long press on the round that you would like to edit or delete.
        \n\nGenerally, the game ends when the first player reaches a score of <b>75</b> or higher.
    </string>

    <string name="dialog_title_help_record_round">How to calculate scores?</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_help_record_round">A round is finished when a player plays their last card and yells <b>BLITZ!</b>\n
        \nScores are then calculated by:
        \n  <b>1.</b> Adding one point for each card the player has played in the Dutch Piles
        \n  <b>2.</b> Subtracting two points for each card the player has in their Blitz Pile
        \n\nType in the score for each player in this app and press <b>Save</b> to record!</string>


    <!-- Error dialogs -->
    <string name="error_title_player_name_empty">Empty player name issue</string>
    <string name="error_message_player_name_empty">Please make sure each player\'s name is not empty.</string>

    <string name="error_title_duplicate_name">Duplicate player name issue</string>
    <string name="error_message_duplicate_name">Each player must have a unique name. There are currently players with the same name. Please fix this and try again!</string>

    <string name="error_title_duplicate_icon">Duplicate player icon issue</string>
    <string name="error_message_duplicate_icon">Each player must have a unique icon. There are currently players with the same icon. Please fix this and try again!</string>

    <string name="error_title_duplicate_name_icon">Duplicate player names and icons issues</string>
    <string name="error_message_duplicate_name_icon">Each player must have a unique name and icon. There are currently players with the same name and same icons. Please fix this and try again!</string>

    <string name="error_title_starting_game">Error starting game</string>
    <string name="error_message_starting_game">Something has gone seriously wrong.
        Confirm that player names are unique!
        If it still does not work, contact me via the Settings page.</string>

    <string name="error_title_score_empty">Empty score issue</string>
    <string name="error_message_score_empty">Please make sure all fields are filled out with valid numbers and then try again.</string>

    <string name="error_title_record_round">Error recording round</string>
    <string name="error_message_record_round">Something has gone seriously wrong.
        Confirm that each player\'s score is filled out.
        If it still does not work, contact me via the Settings page.</string>


</resources>